<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyCountryProfilDemo</string>
    <string name="bangladesh_button">bangladesh</string>
    <string name="india_button">india</string>
    <string name="usa_button">USA</string>


    <string name="banglasesh_text">

        Modern Bangladesh emerged as an independent nation in 1971 after \n\n
        breaking away and achieving independence from Pakistan in the Bangladesh\n
        Liberation War. The country\'s borders corresponded with the major portion \n
        of the ancient and historic region of Bengal in the eastern part of the \n
        Indian subcontinent, where civilization dates back over four millennia, to \n
        the Chalcolithic. The history of the region is closely intertwined with the \n
        history of Bengal and the broader history of the Indian subcontinent.\n


    </string>

    <string name="india_text">
        According to consensus in modern genetics anatomically modern humans first\n\n
        arrived on the Indian subcontinent from Africa between 73,000 and 55,000 years\n
        ago.[1] However, the earliest known human remains in South Asia date to 30,000\n
        years ago. Settled life, which involves the transition from foraging to farming\n
        and pastoralism, began in South Asia around 7,000 BCE. At the site of Mehrgarh,\n
        Balochistan, Pakistan, presence can be documented of the domestication of wheat\n
        and barley, rapidly followed by that of goats, sheep, and cattle.[2] By 4,500 \n
        BCE, settled life had spread more widely,[2] and began to gradually evolve into\n
        the Indus Valley Civilization, an early civilization of the Old world,\n


    </string>
    <string name="usa_text">

         The history of the United States, a country in North America,\n
        began with the arrival of Indigenous people from Siberia before 15,000 BC.\n
        Numerous cultures formed, and many disappeared before 1500. The arrival of\n
        Christopher Columbus in the year 1492 started the European colonization of\n
        the Americas. Most colonies were formed after 1600, and the early records and\n
        writings of John Winthrop make the United States the first nation whose most\n
        distant origins are fully recorded.[1] By the 1760s, thirteen British colonies\n
        contained 2.5 million people along the Atlantic coast east of the Appalachian\n

    </string>


</resources>
